export const topick10 = [
  {
    question: 'Which port is the main one in Ostend today?',
    options: {
      a: 'Western Port',
      b: 'Eastern Port',
      c: 'Southern Port',
    },
    answer: 'Eastern Port',
  },
  {
    question:
      'In what year was the new terminal for passenger ships opened in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: '2000',
      b: '2010',
      c: '2020',
    },
    answer: '2010',
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of vessels are most frequently used in Ostend today?',
    options: {
      a: 'Cargo ships',
      b: 'Fishing boats',
      c: 'Passenger ships',
    },
    answer: 'Passenger ships',
  },
  {
    question: 'What ship is the symbol of modern Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'King Albert',
      b: 'Queen Elizabeth',
      c: 'Princess Elisabeth',
    },
    answer: 'Princess Elisabeth',
  },
  {
    question:
      'In what year was the modernization of the port of Ostend carried out?',
    options: {
      a: '2005',
      b: '2015',
      c: '2025',
    },
    answer: '2015',
  },
  {
    question: 'What structure was built in Ostend to improve marine tourism?',
    options: {
      a: 'New lighthouse',
      b: 'Maritime museum',
      c: 'Maritime exchange',
    },
    answer: 'Maritime museum',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What type of maritime transportation is most developed in Ostend today?',
    options: {
      a: 'Cargo transportation',
      b: 'Passenger transportation',
      c: 'Fishing transportation',
    },
    answer: 'Passenger transportation',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What vessel was the first modern passenger ship to dock in Ostend?',
    options: {
      a: 'King Albert',
      b: 'Queen Elizabeth',
      c: 'Princess Elisabeth',
    },
    answer: 'Princess Elisabeth',
  },
  {
    question:
      'In what year was the reconstruction of the maritime terminal in Ostend carried out?',
    options: {
      a: '2000',
      b: '2010',
      c: '2020',
    },
    answer: '2020',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What structure was built in Ostend to improve cargo transportation?',
    options: {
      a: 'New dock',
      b: 'New bridge',
      c: 'New dam',
    },
    answer: 'New dock',
  },
];
